Inventory of the Papers of Judge John W. Bissell, 1983-2005
University of Virginia, Arthur J. Morris Law Library
- Papers, 1994 (Box 38-42)
  - Jones v. Edminston 1994 June 28 (Box 39)
  - Joyce v. RJR Nabisco Holdings Corp. 1994 May 02 (Box 40)
  - Kesedar v. Sun Co. 1994 November 04 (Box 40)
  - Koren v. Beyer 1994 January 12 (Box 40)
  - Kramer v. Gen. Automation 1994 November 14 (Box 40)
  - Lahood v. Baldini 1994 July 07 (Box 40)
    Energy prices
    Energy assistance for the poor and aged
  - Lanza v. Crystall Commc'n 1994 April 27 (Box 40)
  - Lalomia v. Dickstein, Shapiro, & Morin 1994 November 10 (Box 40)
  - Leak v. Comey 1994 June 22 (Box 40)
  - Linnell v. Siemens Aktiengesellsschaft 1994 November 01 (Box 40)
  - Llarena v. N. Bergen Post Office 1994 October 19 (Box 40)
  - Llarena v. Miller 1994 June 14 (Box 40)
  - Manna v. U.S. Dep't of Justice 1994 April 13 (Box 40)
    Opinion; Order | Opinion; Order (1994 November 04)
    Department of Justice
  - Martin v. Arvonio 1994 April 18 (Box 40)
  - McDonald v. Fauver 1994 September 20 (Box 40)
  - McNeil v. Vt. Slate & Copper Serv. 1994 December 30 (Box 40)
  - Meagher v. United States 1994 October 31 (Box 40)
  - Merola v. Beyer 1994 February 08 (Box 40)
  - Mitchell v. United States 1994 October 31 (Box 40)
  - In re Mola 1994 November 04 (Box 40)
  - Moretti v. State 1994 March 07 (Box 40)
  - Mosley v. N.J. State Parole Bd. 1994 June 07 (Box 40)
  - Moss v. United States 1994 February 01 (Box 40)
  - Murphy v. Ferguson 1994 June 28 (Box 40)
  - Myrie v. Ranco 1994 November 22 (Box 40)
  - Natale v. State 1994 January 14 (Box 40)
    Crime prevention
  - Natural Res. Def. Council v. U.S. Envtl. Prot. Agency 1994 September 21 (Box 40)
  - Niedermaier v. Passaic County Super. Ct. 1994 May 18 (Box 40)
  - N. Am. Philips Corp. v. Columbia Assoc. 1994 January 27 (Box 40)
    Opinion; Order | Opinion (1994 June 13); Order | Opinion (1994 June 16); Order
  - Oakwood Assoc. v. Resolution Trust Corp. 1994 February 01 (Box 41)
  - Outlet City, Inc. v. W. Chem. Prod. 1994 January 10 (Box 41)
    Opinion; Order | Opinion (1994 June 29); Order
  - Pasley v. Edminston 1994 December 05 (Box 41)
  - Passaic Metal Prod. v. Lexington Ins. Co. 1994 June 29 (Box 41)
  - Pearle v. Budesheim 1994 March 24 (Box 41)
  - Peia v. Police Dep't of Franklin 1994 July 07 (Box 41)
  - Perlmutter v. Cooper 1994 June 07 (Box 41)
    Opinion; Order | Opinion; Order (1994 August 23)
  - Pickett v. Essex County Jail 1994 June 23 (Box 41)
  - Pierce v. Int'l Bhd. of Teamsters, Local 863 1994 January 12 (Box 41)
  - Powertex v. Insta-Bulk 1994 November 03 (Box 41)
  - Principal Mut. Life Ins. Co. v. Nicholson 1994 June 30 (Box 41)
    Principal Mut. Life Ins. Co. v. Nicholson, No. 93-433, 1994 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 21750 (D. N.J. June 30, 1994).
  - Ramos v. Office of the Pub. Defender 1994 May 11 (Box 41)
  - Rein v. Newton 1994 October 27 (Box 41)
  - Roberson v. Grundy 1994 December 05 (Box 41)
  - Robinson v. Reiss 1994 May 10 (Box 41)
  - Rodetsky v. Carlson 1994 April 07 (Box 41)
  - Salaam v. Arvonio 1994 April 19 (Box 41)
  - Sanchez v. Sec'y of Health & Human Serv. 1994 March 29 (Box 41)
  - Sauro v. Motorola Corp. 1994 August 09 (Box 41)
    Opinion; Order | Opinion (1994 November 04); Order
    Illinois
  - Schaefer v. Fusco 1994 October 19 (Box 42)
  - Schmidt v. Cohen 1994 July 11 (Box 42)
  - Schmidt v. Seagal 1994 July 11 (Box 42)
  - Serbin v. Innovo Group 1994 April 26 (Box 42)
    Opinion; Order | Opinion (1994 September 29); Order
  - Sharpton v. Passaic County Sheriff Dep't 1994 May 11 (Box 42)
  - Smith v. U.S. Postal Serv. 1994 November 15 (Box 42)
  - In re Snipes 1994 November 17 (Box 42)
    Opinion; Order; Order amending Opinion
  - Stancil v. Arvonio 1994 November 07 (Box 42)
  - Summit Enter. v. W. Trucking, Inc. 1994 January 19 (Box 42)
  - Surgical Sys. & Instruments v. C.R. Bard, Inc. 1994 September 20 (Box 42)
  - Sussex & Warren Holding Corp. v. State 1994 April 12 (Box 42)
    General public lands matters
  - Taylor v. Englehardt 1994 January 06 (Box 42)
  - Teamsters-Employers Pension Fund, Local No. 945 v. T. Farese & Sons 1994 October 12 (Box 42)
  - Terrell v. Beyer 1994 November 02 (Box 42)
  - Tucker v. Brennan 1994 November 22 (Box 42)
  - Ullrich v. Sears Roebuck & Co. 1994 March 31 (Box 42)
  - United States v. Austin 1994 May 18 (Box 42)
  - United States v. LaBarck 1994 November 10 (Box 42)
  - United States v. Pakenham 1994 December 06 (Box 42)
  - United States v. Pieri 1994 July 25 (Box 42)
  - United States v. Spatola 1994 November 16 (Box 42)
    Opinion; Letter from Gerald Shur to Antonio Spatola (1992 April 14); Order (1994 November 16)
    Italy
  - Wakefield v. Arvonio 1994 May 10 (Box 42)
  - Wakefield v. Borough of North Plainfield 1994 July 29 (Box 42)
  - Ware v. Michelman 1994 October 28 (Box 42)
  - Weiss v. Mercedes-Benz of N. Am. 1994 February 24 (Box 42)
  - West v. All Am. Sports 1994 October 14 (Box 42)
  - Westinghouse Credit Corp. v. D'Annunzio 1994 July 11 (Box 42)
  - Wilson v. United States 1994 August 08 (Box 42)
  - Witco Corp. v. Travelers Indem. Co. 1994 April 06 (Box 42)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion (1994 August 05); Order
    Witco Corp. v. Travelers Indem. Co., No. 93-4709, 1994 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 20781 (D. N.J. Apr. 6, 1994).
  - Worsley v. U.S. Marshal Serv. 1994 October 13 (Box 42)
  - Zarif v. Barbo 1994 October 19 (Box 42)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion (1994 December 05); Order
- Papers, 1995 (Box 43-46)
  All papers dated 1995.
  - Abadeer v. Arab Banking Corp. 1995 July 31 (Box 43)
    Bahrain
  - In re Alcon Demolition 1995 August 02 (Box 43)
  - Alford v. Sec'y of the U.S. Dep't of Health & Human Serv. 1995 March 03 (Box 43)
    Alford v. Sec'y of the U.S. Dep't of Health & Human Serv., 934 F. Supp. 134 (D. N.J. 1995).
  - Alpine Lace Brands v. Kraft Foods 1995 October 31 (Box 43)
  - Arias v. Middlesex County Adult Corr. Ctr. 1995 January 05 (Box 43)
  - Bartell v. Travelers Ins. Co. 1995 January 09 (Box 43)
  - Best v. Morton 1995 July 12 (Box 43)
  - Boeglin v. Home Care Mgmt. Serv. 1995 November 21 (Box 43)
  - Brown v. Int'l Bhd. of Elec. Workers, Local No. 52 1995 September 28 (Box 43)
    Opinion; Order; Exhibit A | Opinion (1995 December 27); Order; Amended Complaint
  - Buechel v. DePuy 1995 September 18 (Box 43)
  - Candelario v. J & S Ford P'ship 1995 September 29 (Box 43)
  - Centennial Life Ins. Co. v. Gold 1995 August 04 (Box 43)
  - Cent. Mut. Ins. Co. v. Battaglia 1995 December 04 (Box 43)
    Adoption and foster care
  - Cooney v. Mullaney 1995 January 10 (Box 43)
  - Crossroads Cogeneration Corp. v. Cooper Indus. 1995 September 29 (Box 43)
  - Dammer v. Mercedes-Benz of N. Am. 1995 April 06 (Box 43)
  - DeSalvo v. Sapolsky 1995 February 07 (Box 43)
  - Doherty v. Teamsters Pension Trust Fund 1995 December 29 (Box 43)
  - Donnell v. Englehardt 1995 August 03 (Box 43)
  - Durex, Inc. v. Int'l Bhd. of Teamsters, Local Union No. 97 1995 February 23 (Box 43)
  - Evergreen Am. Corp. v. Pomeroy 1995 October 31 (Box 43)
    Public participation and lobbying
    Immigrant health and welfare
  - Faison v. U.S. Parole Comm'n 1995 April 19 (Box 43)
  - Farrakhan v. Arvonio 1995 August 17 (Box 43)
  - Fed. Deposit Ins. Corp. v. Garidis 1995 November 17 (Box 43)
  - Fed. Deposit Ins. Corp. v. Linda Court, Inc. 1995 May 31 (Box 43)
  - Fed. Deposit Ins. Corp. v. Progressive Cas. Ins. Co. 1995 October 31 (Box 43)
    Opinion; Order (x2)
  - Ferriol v. Allstate Ins. Co. 1995 January 18 (Box 43)
  - Ford v. Shalala 1995 March 20 (Box 43)
    Opinion; Order (1995 March 21)
  - Franklin v. Pa. Truck Lines 1995 September 28 (Box 43)
  - Frants v. CIT Group 1995 March 22 (Box 43)
  - Gonzalez v. Hudson County Jail 1995 August 21 (Box 44)
  - Gramuglia v. Sender 1995 December 13 (Box 44)
  - Green v. Morton 1995 October 12 (Box 44)
  - Green v. Shalala 1995 June 12 (Box 44)
  - Hakeem v. Fauver 1995 February 15 (Box 44)
  - Holmes v. Wilson 1995 July 20 (Box 44)
  - Int'l Bhd. of Teamsters, Local 522 v. Joule Maint. Corp. 1995 February 07 (Box 44)
    Opinion; Order; Exhibit F; Complaint
  - Jacobs v. Stephens 1995 January 06 (Box 44)
    Opinion; Order | Opinion(1995 March 02); Order | Opinion(1995 May 25); Order
  - Jones v. Sec'y of the U.S. Dep't of Health & Human Serv. 1995 February 27 (Box 44)
  - Kato v. Fauver 1995 January 06 (Box 44)
  - Keller v. Orix Credit Alliance 1995 April 06 (Box 44)
  - Kierstead v. Suter 1995 November 21 (Box 44)
    Opinion; Order; Exhibit A; Exhibit B; Exhibit C; Affidavit of Indigency; Exhibit H; Addendum to Affidavit of Indigency; Exhibit J
  - Kohn v. Travelers Ins. Co. 1995 May 05 (Box 44)
  - Kramer v. United Ass'n of Journeymen & Apprentices 1995 September 29 (Box 44)
    Opinion; Order; Order Admitting Counsel Pro Hac Vice
  - Laborers Local Union No. 472 & 172 Welfare & Pension Funds v. Carbro Constr. Corp. 1995 July 13 (Box 44)
  - Lagoey v. Immaculate Conception Ukrainian Catholic Church 1995 January 27 (Box 44)
  - Levi v. Texaco Ref. & Mktg. 1995 August 02 (Box 44)
  - Licata v. Ginnotti 1995 September 12 (Box 44)
  - Liebeskind v. Wilson, Elser, Moskowitz, Eelman, & Dicker 1995 April 06 (Box 44)
    Opinion; Order | Opinion(1995 June 06); Order | Opinion(1995 June 15); Order
  - Linear Dynamics v. A.H. Harris & Sons 1995 October 06 (Box 44)
  - Limite v. Fauver 1995 March 13 (Box 44)
  - Linnell v. Siemens Corp. 1995 January 11 (Box 44)
  - Manis v. Twp. of Millburn 1995 January 12 (Box 44)
  - Marcelle v. Motel 6 1995 April 06 (Box 44)
    Florida
  - Marincas v. Lewis 1995 June 20 (Box 44)
    Opinion; Order; Exhibit A; Exhibit B
  - Martinez v. Butler 1995 May 01 (Box 44)
  - Maymi v. Arvonio 1995 May 04 (Box 45)
  - McKnight v. Ohio Cas. Ins. Co. 1995 March 30 (Box 45)
  - MCI Telecomm. v. Costamar Travel Cruise & Tours 1995 July 11 (Box 45)
  - Medlinksy v. Matsushita Elec. Corp. 1995 October 24 (Box 45)
    Opinion (x2)
  - Microstar Computers v. Laptops, Etc. Corp. 1995 April 26 (Box 45)
    Maryland
  - Moore v. Engleheart 1995 October 25 (Box 45)
  - Moretti v. State 1995 June 12 (Box 45)
  - Mourad v. O'Halloran 1995 April 19 (Box 45)
  - Muhammad v. Dep't of Corr. 1995 September 12 (Box 45)
  - Munro v. Employee Benefit Plans 1995 March 02 (Box 45)
    Opinion; Order | Opinion (1995 August 17); Order
  - Nance v. City of Newark Police Dep't 1995 May 25 (Box 45)
  - Navarro v. Shalala 1995 June 14 (Box 45)
  - N.P. v. Kinnelon Bd. of Ed. 1995 October 30 (Box 45)
  - N.J. State Council of Carpenters v. Beta Contractors 1995 January 06 (Box 45)
  - Newport Assoc. Dev. Co. v. Travelers Indem. Co. 1995 March 21 (Box 45)
    Newport Assoc. Dev. Co. v. Travelers Indem. Co., No. 94-1514, 1995 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 22010 (D. N.J. Mar. 21, 1995).
  - Noorilly v. Betts Corp. 1995 August 17 (Box 45)
  - Oquendo v. Sec'y of Health & Human Serv. 1995 July 21 (Box 45)
  - Ortiz v. City of New Brunswick 1995 October 31 (Box 45)
  - Pascarell v. Nat'l Office Supply Co. 1995 June 22 (Box 45)
  - Patel v. United States 1995 August 04 (Box 45)
  - Paterson v. Scherer 1995 January 19 (Box 45)
    Opinion; Order transferring case to Bankruptcy Court
  - Pierce v. Paul's Trucking Co. 1995 October 06 (Box 45)
  - Pierre v. Chater 1995 July 13 (Box 45)
  - Pray v. Internal Revenue Serv. 1995 February 15 (Box 45)
  - Price v. State 1995 July 08 (Box 45)
  - Raine v. Worldvision Enter. 1995 October 31 (Box 45)
  - Ravenell v. Fallon 1995 February 15 (Box 45)
  - Redfern v. Green 1995 January 05 (Box 45)
  - Reevy v. United States 1995 December 04 (Box 45)
  - Remington Rand Corp. v. Bus. Sys., Inc. 1995 June 01 (Box 45)
    Opinion; Exhibit A; Exhibit B; Exhibit C; Exhibit D; Order
  - Restrepo v. Sec'y of Health & Human Serv. 1995 February 06 (Box 45)
  - Revell v. Sec'y of Health & Human Serv. 1995 April 19 (Box 46)
  - Riether v. AmBase Corp. 1995 February 27 (Box 46)
  - Rodriguez v. Sec'y of the Dep't of Health & Human Serv. 1995 July 10 (Box 46)
  - Santaita v. Shalala 1995 April 06 (Box 46)
  - Santiago v. Sec'y of the Dep't of Health & Human Serv. 1995 March 17 (Box 46)
  - Santos v. Van Leeuwen Pipe & Tube Corp. 1995 October 31 (Box 46)
  - Serbin v. Innovo Group 1995 July 20 (Box 46)
  - Sethi v. Southland Corp. 1995 December 06 (Box 46)
  - Slapikas v. J.H. Cohn Software Assoc. 1995 January 19 (Box 46)
  - Smith v. United States 1995 October 24 (Box 46)
  - Spartan Inter-Trans Group v. Connor Container Express 1995 June 07 (Box 46)
    Opinion; Opinion
  - Starbare III Partners v. St. Lawrence Corp. 1995 July 05 (Box 46)
  - Steele v. Vazquez 1995 November 07 (Box 46)
  - Storm v. Woodbridge Twp. 1995 November 07 (Box 46)
  - Sullivan v. Shalala 1995 July 11 (Box 46)
  - Telepo v. Whitman 1995 November 30 (Box 46)
    Letter-Opinion; Exhibit A; Order
  - Tobia v. Sec'y of the U.S. Dep't of Health & Human Serv. 1995 May 04 (Box 46)
  - Transmodal Assoc. v. Leonard Lang Imp. 1995 September 22 (Box 46)
  - Tucker v. United States 1995 December 08 (Box 46)
  - United States v. All Shares of Stock of R.S. Cars 1995 May 31 (Box 46)
  - United States v. Berry 1995 July 12 (Box 46)
  - United States v. Okoro 1995 September 14 (Box 46)
    Nigeria
  - United States v. Scarafile 1995 January 10 (Box 46)
  - Weiss v. Mercedes-Benz of N. Am. 1995 May 11 (Box 46)
    Weiss v. Mercedes-Benz of N. Am., 899 F. Supp. 1297 (D. N.J. 1995).
  - Williams v. N. State Prison 1995 September 12 (Box 46)
  - Windsoft v. Intercon Sys. 1995 September 22 (Box 46)
    Windsoft v. Intercon Sys., No. 95-1858, 1995 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 21294 (D. N.J. Sept. 22, 1995).
  - Witco Corp. v. Travelers Indem. Co. 1995 February 01 (Box 46)
    Opinion; Order | Opinion (1995 May 02); Order
  - Wood v. Qudeen 1995 April 24 (Box 46)
  - Zarif v. Barbo 1995 March 22 (Box 46)
- Papers, 1996 (Box 47-50)
  All papers dated 1996.
  - Abdulsamad v. State 1996 July 17 (Box 47)
  - Alpine Lace Brands v. Kraft Foods 1996 March 21 (Box 47)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (1996 September 20)
  - Annun v. Orval Kent Foods Co. 1996 January 05 (Box 47)
  - Artistic Doors & Windows v. Artistic Window & Door 1996 July 19 (Box 47)
  - Bender v. Chater 1996 July 30 (Box 47)
  - Boguslavsky v. Hosman 1996 May 03 (Box 47)
  - Boettcher v. Chater 1996 March 04 (Box 47)
  - Brown v. Foster 1996 December 13 (Box 47)
  - Carvajal v. Transport Workers Union Local 1400 1996 April 24 (Box 47)
  - Centennial Life Ins. Co. v. Gold 1996 January 05 (Box 47)
  - Chalkias v. Monarch Life Ins. Co. 1996 October 18 (Box 47)
  - Christian v. Latimer 1996 March 05 (Box 47)
  - Chubb & Son v. Cerbone 1996 July 24 (Box 47)
  - C.M. v. Bd. of Ed. of Union County 1996 May 03 (Box 47)
    Opinion; Opinion (1996 July 29); Meeting Notes; Order; Amended Opinion
  - In re Coin-Telecomm. 1996 November 20 (Box 47)
    Opinion; Exhibit I; Financing Statement (1996 September 20); Order (1996 November 20)
    In re Coin-Telecomm., No. 96-2155, 1996 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 22665 (D. N.J. Nov. 20, 1996).
  - Cuttitta v. Guzman 1996 May 29 (Box 47)
  - Daniels v. Thomas & Betts Corp. 1996 October 17 (Box 47)
  - Dempsey v. Sohl 1996 August 02 (Box 47)
    Opinion; Order to proceed In Forma Pauperis
  - Depuy v. Biomedical Eng'g Trust 1996 December 12 (Box 47)
  - Doering v. Copper Mountain Ski Resort 1996 August 06 (Box 47)
    Opinion; Order of Transfer
  - Donnelly v. N.J. Highway Auth. 1996 February 07 (Box 47)
  - Drisco v. Poncho 1996 May 15 (Box 47)
  - Dynasty Fine Oriental Rugs v. Merchants & Business Men's Mut. 1996 December 18 (Box 47)
  - Enprotech Corp. v. Renda 1996 January 17 (Box 47)
  - Evergreen Am. Corp. v. Reno 1996 April 24 (Box 47)
  - Fed. Deposit Ins. Corp. v. Garidis 1996 February 20 (Box 47)
  - Fed. Deposit Ins. Corp. v. Nat'l Union Fire Ins. Co. 1996 December 12 (Box 47)
  - Fed. Deposit Ins. Corp. v. Progressive Cas. Ins. Co. 1996 January 18 (Box 47)
  - First Interregional Advisors Co. v. Scherers Commc'n 1996 February 01 (Box 47)
    Ohio
  - Fischman v. Margolis 1996 March 26 (Box 47)
  - Flemmings v. Morton 1996 August 08 (Box 47)
  - Ford v. Brooks-Sloate Terrace Coop. Ass'n 1996 March 18 (Box 47)
  - Fuller v. Town of Dover 1996 May 30 (Box 47)
  - Gallant v. Telebrands Corp. 1996 March 04 (Box 48)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (1996 May 03)
    Canada
  - Gambino v. Morris 1996 April 11 (Box 48)
  - Garcia v. Morton 1996 July 26 (Box 48)
  - George v. Fava 1996 April 12 (Box 48)
  - Glebar Co. v. Royal Master Grinders 1996 March 22 (Box 48)
    Glebar Co. v. Royal Master Grinders, No. 96-403, 1996 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 13041 (D. N.J. Mar. 22, 1996).
  - Goldfarb v. Cunard Lines 1996 January 26 (Box 48)
    Opinion; Letter; Letter; Proposed Order; Opinion; Order (1996 April 08)
  - Goldman v. Metro. Life Ins. Co. 1996 July 31 (Box 48)
    Opinion; Order Granting Motion to Remand
  - Grabner v. John Alden Life Ins. Co. 1996 September 20 (Box 48)
  - Green v. Morton 1996 September 24 (Box 48)
  - Hampton v. O'Leary 1996 March 08 (Box 48)
    Missouri
  - Herrera v. Barbo 1996 August 06 (Box 48)
  - Holmes v. Runyon 1996 April 01 (Box 48)
  - Indus. Network Sys. v. Armstrong World Indus. 1996 April 17 (Box 48)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (1996 May 21)
  - Isaacs v. Frost 1996 January 24 (Box 48)
  - J. I. Hass Co. v. Gilbane Bldg. Co. 1996 August 26 (Box 48)
  - Joyce v. RJR Nabisco Holding Corp. 1996 June 13 (Box 48)
  - Keep v. Children's Aid & Adoption Soc'y of N.J. 1996 March 19 (Box 48)
  - Kenny v. Anthony R. Davis Agency 1996 September 03 (Box 48)
  - Kuczynski v. Daxton Indus. 1996 May 29 (Box 48)
  - LaNeve v. W. Milford Med. Ctr. 1996 May 30 (Box 48)
    Opinion; Order; Order (1996 June 06)
  - Linear Dynamics v. A.H. Harris & Sons 1996 February 08 (Box 48)
  - Llarena v. Soc. Sec. Admin. 1996 August 08 (Box 48)
  - Marchitto v. Connelly 1996 July 12 (Box 48)
    Opinion; Order and Preliminary Injunction
  - Manning v. D'Alessio 1996 July 26 (Box 48)
  - Marrero v. Rettenburg 1996 March 11 (Box 48)
  - In re McCormack 1996 December 13 (Box 48)
  - Melvin v. State 1996 March 05 (Box 48)
  - Metro. Life Ins. Co. v. Brose 1996 August 30 (Box 48)
  - Metzler v. Westinghouse Elec. Corp. 1996 November 22 (Box 48)
  - Miscik v. Chater 1996 July 16 (Box 48)
  - Molnar v. Sears Roebuck & Co. 1996 October 04 (Box 48)
  - Morris v. Davidson 1996 December 04 (Box 48)
  - Moss v. United States 1996 April 08 (Box 48)
    Veterans' organizations and recognition
    Veterans' education, employment, rehabilitation
    Veterans' loans, housing, homeless programs
  - Mulligan v. Delicato Vineyards 1996 February 02 (Box 48)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (1996 March 18)
    Mulligan v. Delicato Vineyards, No. 95-3281, 1996 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 10080 (D. N.J. Feb. 2, 1996).
  - Murphy v. Enesco Corp. 1996 June 05 (Box 48)
  - Nance v. City of Newark Police Dep't 1996 January 03 (Box 49)
  - N.J. Turnpike Ass'n v. PPG Indus. 1996 March 06 (Box 49)
  - New Valley Corp. v. Lexington Ins. Co. 1996 July 11 (Box 49)
  - Obiukwu v. State 1996 July 18 (Box 49)
  - Ortiz v. City of New Brunswick 1996 February 20 (Box 49)
  - Old Bridge Owners Coop. Corp. v. Twp. of Old Bridge 1996 March 07 (Box 49)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion (1996 June 13); Order; Opinion (1996 July 23); Order; Opinion (1996 January 11); Order
    Old Bridge Owners Coop. Corp. v. Twp. of Old Bridge, 914 F. Supp. 1059 (D. N.J. 1996).
  - Pierce v. Int'l Bhd. of Teamsters, Local 863 1996 April 19 (Box 49)
  - Pray v. Internal Revenue Serv. 1996 July 31 (Box 49)
    Pray v. Internal Revenue Serv., No. 95-794, 1996 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 11643 (D. N.J. July 31, 1996).
  - Quintana v. Arvonio 1996 January 03 (Box 49)
  - Rajin v. United States 1996 October 25 (Box 49)
  - Rand McNally & Co. v. Lang 1996 January 22 (Box 49)
  - Reyes v. Morton 1996 May 03 (Box 49)
  - Richardson v. Mike 1996 February 09 (Box 49)
  - Rodriguez v. Chater 1996 July 19 (Box 49)
  - Rutkowski v. Middlesex Borough Police Dep't 1996 January 11 (Box 49)
  - Rycoline Prod. v. C&W Unlimited 1996 November 20 (Box 49)
  - Saltzman v. Ceco Filters 1996 March 06 (Box 49)
  - Sayyed v. LSG/SKY CHEFS 1996 December 31 (Box 49)
  - Schnorrbush v. United States 1996 May 29 (Box 49)
  - Schreiber Foods v. Am. Nat'l Fire Ins. Co. 1996 April 01 (Box 49)
  - Seidenbaum v. Cont'l Airlines 1996 January 29 (Box 49)
  - Steele v. Vazquez 1996 February 28 (Box 49)
  - Storm v. Woodbridge Twp. 1996 April 07 (Box 49)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion (1996 November 07); Order; Opinion (1996 November 13); Order; Opinion (1996 November 08); Order
  - Stretch Devices v. Charles M. Jessup, Inc. 1996 May 03 (Box 50)
  - Tarczynski v. Fauver 1996 December 17 (Box 50)
  - Town v. Bausch & Lomb 1996 August 08 (Box 50)
    Australia
    Malaysia
  - Transmodal Assoc. v. Leonard Lang Imp. 1996 February 20 (Box 50)
  - Trump Taj Mahal Assoc. v. DCA 1996 July 25 (Box 50)
  - In 2175 Lemoine Ave. Corp. 1996 October 25 (Box 50)
  - United States v. Ahkami 1996 February 20 (Box 50)
  - United States v. Carlson 1996 January 23 (Box 50)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (1996 February 28)
  - United States v. One 1993 Porsche 911 Cabriolet Auto. 1996 August 05 (Box 50)
  - United States v. Lebowitz 1996 July 11 (Box 50)
    Hong Kong
  - United States v. Stansfield 1996 September 11 (Box 50)
    Opinion (Opinion of U.S.C.J. Cowen)
  - United States v. Wright 1996 August 05 (Box 50)
  - Vitiello v. Paton 1996 March 26 (Box 50)
  - Winstead v. State 1996 October 24 (Box 50)
  - Worldlink Logistics v. Nat'l Shipping Co. of Saudi Arabia 1996 October 03 (Box 50)
    Saudi Arabia
  - Witco Corp. v. Travelers Indem. Co. 1996 April 19 (Box 50)
  - W.P. v. Poritz 1996 March 15 (Box 50)
    Opinion; Order Certifying a Class; Opinion; Order (1996 July 01); Order Amending Opinion (1996 July 02)
    W.P. v. Poritz, 931 F. Supp. 1187 (D. N.J. 1996).
  - Zenith Lab. v. Abbott Lab. 1996 August 05 (Box 50)
- Papers, 1997 (Box 51-54)
  All papers dated 1997.
  - Abrams v. Comm'r 1997 October 20 (Box 51)
  - Alpine Lace Brands v. Kraft Foods 1997 April 10 (Box 51)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion (1997 July 11); Order; Opinion (1997 September 23); Order
  - Amloid Corp. v. Moose Mountain Mktg. 1997 September 19 (Box 51)
  - Appalachian Ins. Co. v. Port Auth. 1997 March 17 (Box 51)
  - Askander v. Pressler & Pressler 1997 April 02 (Box 51)
  - Awad v. State 1997 January 22 (Box 51)
  - Aziz v. Dep't of Corr. 1997 January 21 (Box 51)
  - Barclay v. County of Middlesex 1997 October 23 (Box 51)
  - Bass v. Kossup 1997 October 30 (Box 51)
  - Bishop v. Maersk 1997 April 10 (Box 51)
    Kenya
  - Boatman v. State 1997 September 18 (Box 51)
  - Boguslavsky v. Hosman 1997 August 18 (Box 51)
  - Bosch v. Chater 1997 January 09 (Box 51)
  - Bush Boak Allen v. Clearly Canadian Beverage Corp. 1997 April 03 (Box 51)
    Virginia
  - Carvajal v. Transport Workers Union Local 1400 1997 March 26 (Box 51)
  - Centennial Life Ins. Co. v. Gold 1997 March 21 (Box 51)
    Opinion; Order; Opinion; Order (1997 June 03); Opinion; Order (1997 August 18); Order Amending Opinion (1997 September 04)
  - In re Checkwood 1997 April 24 (Box 51)
  - Chubb & Son v. Cerbone 1997 July 07 (Box 51)
  - Ciardi v. De Maria 1997 October 20 (Box 51)
    Opinion; Attorney Letter; Attorney Letter
  - Chiloro v. Ross 1997 February 26 (Box 51)
  - Copelco Capital v. Mitchell Co. 1997 December 15 (Box 51)
    Alabama
  - Cray v. City of Elizabeth 1997 December 02 (Box 51)
  - Crossroads Cogeneration Corp. v. Orange & Rockland Util. 1997 June 30 (Box 51)
    Crossroads Cogeneration Corp. v. Orange & Rockland Util., 969 F. Supp. 907 (D. N.J. 1997).
  - Damon v. United States 1997 October 09 (Box 51)
  - Denman v. N.J. Transit 1997 May 29 (Box 51)
  - Dompor v. Citibank 1997 December 12 (Box 51)
  - Enprotech Corp. v. Renda 1997 November 06 (Box 51)
  - Estrada v. Comm'r 1997 December 12 (Box 51)